Welcome to the
eLearning session,
欢迎来到 elearning 课程
Getting Started with
Settings of HL7 Components.
Ensemble 和 HL7 设置入门课程
When you create an
age （？） HL7 Production,
当你创建一个 HL7 Production 时，
you can automatically
add pre-built components
你可以自动地添加预制的组件
which simplify setting
up an HL7 environment.
其可以简化 HL7 环境设置。
We'll talk about some of
the most important settings
我们会讲解各种组件
for each type of
the component, learn
一些重要的设置，学习
how to find more information
about a particular setting,
如何查找一些特定设置的详细信息，
and configure default settings.
以及配置成缺省设置。
Let's first look at
Business Services.
首先我们来看一下 Business Service.
Each Business Service has an
adapter associated with it
每个 Business Service 有一个适配器 (Adapter)与之关联
that abstracts the connection
with the client application.
其抽象出应用客户端的连接。
There are many different
pre-built adapters,
这里有非常多的不同种类的预制适配器，
such as TCP, File,
HTTP, FTP, and SOAP.
比如 TCP，文件，HTTP, FTP 和 SOAP 等。
Based on the adapter that
the Business Service uses,
基于Business Service 所使用的不同的适配器，
the list of settings can vary.
配置列表会有变化。
We can see which adaptor
a Business Service uses,
我们可以根据适配器类名
by looking at the adapter
class name setting.
来判断一个 Business Service 所用的适配器
For this one, we can see that
this Business Service is using
比如，我们看到这个 Business Service
the EnsLib.File.InboundAdapter.
用的是 EnsLib.File.InboundAdapter.
An example of settings for a
Business Service using a file
这是一个 Business Service 使用的适配器是
adapter are File
Path or File Spec,
文件适配器设置例子，其要设置文件路径和文件规范，
while a Business Service
using a TCP adapter
当一个 Business Service 用 TCP 适配器时
would have a
setting called Port.
会设置端口。
To specify where a
Business Service should
指定一个 Business Service 的消息要发送到什么地方
send its message, we
then need to specify
我们需要指定
a Target Config Name.
一个目标配置的名字。
This can be one, or multiple
Business Processes, or Business
可以是一个，或者多个 Business Process 或者
Operations that a
Business Service
Business Operations，为一个 Business Service
should send its message to.
所要发送消息的目标。
This setting can then
correspond with clicking the dot
这个设置可以通过点击特定组件
for a particular component.
边上相应的“点”。
Notice our Business Service is
currently sending its message
注意到，我们的 Business Service 当前法送消息
to the message router.
到消息路由。
An HL7 Business Service
also has a setting called,
并且 HL7 Business Service 也设置了一
Message Schema Category.
消息 Schema Category.
This setting takes
the schema of messages
这个设置表明了 Ensemble
that Ensemble can
expect to read in
通过 Business Service
through that Business Service.
所期望读入的消息 schema
Specifying this
setting allows Ensemble
指定这个配置允许 Ensemble
to understand the
contents of the message
在校验或者在消息查看器查看消息时
when validating or viewing the
message in the message viewer.
理解消息的内容
For a message router,
we have the ability
对于消息路由，我们有能力
to validate a message
against a schema specified
在一个消息 Schmea Category 中对于 Business Service
in the Message Schema Category
of the Business Service.
依据一个 schema 校验消息
This setting is conveniently
called Validation.
这个设置我们便利地称其为校验 (Validation).
We can simply use a one
to validate or a zero
我们可怀疑简单使用 “1”需要校验，/////////////////////////////////////////////?
to not validate, or we
can set specific flags
或者 "0" 不校验，或则我们可以指定一组
to have more control
over what Ensemble
规范，能更多地由 Ensemble 控制
uses to validate a message.
如何校验消息。
Another important setting
for the message router
对于消息路由，还有一个重要的设置
is Business Rule Name.
就是 业务规则名称(Business Rule Name)
This setting directs us to the
rule set that does the routing.
这个设置可以向我们表明这个路由使用的是什么规则集。
We can click on the magnifying
glass to edit this rule set.
我们可以点击放大镜来编辑规则集。
Like a Business Service,
a Business Operation
如同 Business Service， 一个 Business Operation
has an adapter that modifies
the list of settings available.
也有一个适配器，其有一系列配置。
Here we can see that
To_Lab is using the adapter
这里我们可以看到 To_Lab 使用的适配器是
EnsLib.HL7.Adapt
er.TCPOutboundAdapter.
EnsLib.HL7.Adapter.TCPOutboundAdapter.
For example, a TCP Business
Operation such as this
举例，一个如同这样的 TCP Business Operation
needs to specify
Port and IP Address,
需要指定端口号和 IP 地址，
while a file Business Operation
has File Path and File Name.
正如一个文件 Business Operation 有文件路径和文件名
The Business Operations
failure timeout setting
这个 Business Operation 有失败超时 (failure timeout)设置
is also an important
setting to take a look at.
这也是一个需要关注的重要设置。
This setting determines
how long to keep
这个设置决定在放弃重试前
trying to send a message
out before giving up.
持续多长时间，尝试发送消息。
All components also have
a setting called Enabled.
所有的组件有一个设置为启用(Enabled).
If you would like to
temporarily disable a component,
如果你要暂时停用一个组件，
de-check this box, or you can
double click the component
不选中这个框，或者你双击这个组件
to toggle Enabled.
切换 Enabled.
Notice this component turns
gray when it's disabled.
注意到，停用后，这个组件会变成灰色。
There are many settings
that you can configure,
这里有许多设置你可以进行配置，
but we have just highlighted
a few of the most common ones.
但我们只在这里突现几个最常用的。
If you don't know
what a setting does,
如果你不知道如何设置某一项，
simply click on the
name of the setting
只要简单点击该设置的名称
to get a description
and any documentation.
就可以获取该设置的描述信息和文档。
Once you have modified
a particular component,
如果你修改了某个特定的组件，
make sure to click Apply, or
you will lose your changes.
一定要点"Apply",否则你会丢失你的修改。
It is important to set
up default settings
对你的组件，如何配置成缺省设置
for your components.
也非常重要。
For example, to
specify Port and IP
比如，对于一个 Business Operation
address for Business
Operation, so
指定端口和 IP 地址，
that when you move code
from your test system
为了保证，当你的迁移你的代码到从测试系统
to your live system, it is
reading the correct values
到生产系统的时候，
for that system.
系统读取的是对的数据。
We can view these
default settings
对于一个配置页面
on the configuration
page, by clicking
点击页面上的蓝色箭头
the page with the blue arrow.
我们可以查看缺省的设置。
I can even change a
setting to be the default
我甚至可以在这页面上
value from this page.
修改设置到缺省值。
For example, I can choose
IP Address to be blank,
比如，我可以选在 IP 地址为空，
which is what the default was.
其就是原来的缺省设置。
To set up default
values, we need
将设置设为缺省值，
to go to Ensemble, Configure,
System Default Settings.
我们可以到 Ensemble, Configure, System Default Settings.
Let's set up a new default file
path for a To_Billing Business
让我们来为 To_Billing 设置一个新的缺省路径
Operation.
Notice here, I've set
up MyHospitalHL7Engine.
这里注意到，我对 MyHospitalHL7Engine 进行配置。
My Item Name is To_Billing,
my Setting Name is FilePath,
我的项目的名字是 To_Billing, 我的设置名称是 FilePath,
and my Setting Value
is C:EnsembleHL7Out.
以及我的设置值是 C:EnsembleHL7Out
Notice now when I look
at my default settings
注意，现在，当我看我的 To_Billing 组件
for my To_Billing component, my
final path default value is now
我的缺省设置，我的最终的路径缺省值是
C:EnsembleHL7Out.
If I select that
option and click OK,
如果我选在该选项，并且点击 OK，
my setting name is
now blue, meaning
我的设置名称变成蓝色，其意味着
that I get my value from
my default settings.
我从缺省设置中获取了值。
Thank you for watching
Getting Started with Settings
感谢您收看，HL7 /////////////////////////////////////////////////////???
of HL7 Components.
组件设置入门课程
We hope you learned
a little bit more
我们希望您能从中学习到一点
about settings for the
HL7 pre-built components.
关于如何设置 HL7 的预制组件。